dezrez.com 2017-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Dezrez Services Ltd.

More ____

## Login to your dezrez product

Sales & lettings software

Property management software

## See how Dezrez helps small businesses & enterprises thrive

### See what our software can do - contact us now for a demo

## Find out how Dezrez can help your business succeed

### **Fill out the form to get started**

## Sign up to our newsletter

###### Our market-leading newsletter is an invaluable source for estate agents, letting agents and property management agents , inspiration and learning technology industry news and much more!

## Sign up to our newsletter

## Login to your dezrez product

Sales & lettings software

Property management software

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information.

The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.

  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.

  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

  * We have implemented and use Display Advertising and Google Remarketing to advertise online.

  * You will see our Ads on Third-party vendors websites, including Google, we show our ads on sites across the Internet.

  * Dezrez Services Limited and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to your website.

  * You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ "Google advertising opt-out page") or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "Google Analytics opt-out page").

  * Google has additional information available about their [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746 "Remarketing Privacy Guidelines"), [Policies](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=143465 "Policies"), and [Restrictions](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=178363 "Restrictions").

#### Sending your demo request...

## Success!

### Your request has been sent to our team

Return to dezrez.com

__

## Help & Support Centre

  * __  
DezrezOne technical specs
  * __  
Connect to Support
  * __  
Contact Dezrez

### Chat to our support team

Please provide the following...

No technicians currently available

Live chat allows you to use instant messaging to contact our Support Team. A live chat representative will ask you to describe your problem, and will be able to guide you through possible solutions.

When you are ready, click the Launch Chat button to start talking to a support representative.

### DezrezOne technical specs

The minimum specification for dezrez to function is very basic. An internet connection and rudimentary hardware is often all that's needed. Normally the most basic computers commercially available can support dezrez, though a more specific recommendation can be found in the PDF below.

### Connect to our support agents

Please choose the option as advised by your dezrez support representative.

### Contact details for further assistance

#### 0845 465 2222

Support Option 1

Branding Option 2

Portals Option 3

Accounts Option 4

All other enquiries Option 5

#### E-mail us...

Support support@dezrez.com

Branding templates@dezrez.com

Portals portals@dezrez.com

Accounts accounts@dezrez.com

All other enquiries mail@dezrez.com

You can also contact us via telephone or e-mail.

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept [Read More](http://dezrezwebsite.azurewebsites.net/)

Privacy & Cookies Policy
